Davi Silva Alves de Oliveira

davi.comp.oliveira@gmail.com

Phone: (88) 99766-0734 Fortaleza - CE, Brazil

Profile

Currently working as a fullstack development intern at Elevar Commerce.

I am an undergraduate student in Information Systems at the Federal University of Ceará - Campus Quixadá and a web developer with experience in React, Angular, Node, and other development technologies.

My experiences primarily focus on frontend, but I also work on backend projects using Node and Java.

Check out my projects on **GitHub** or connect with me on **LinkedIn**.

Professional Experience

Dec 2022 - Present | Fullstack Development Intern at Elevar Commerce

• Developing and maintaining web applications for an Ecommerce, including both frontend and backend, as well as integrations and other inherent features of this type of product;

Skills: Angular · Angular JS · Angular Universal · Node · Java · Firebase · SCSS (Sass) · SQL · Rest API · Scrum Methodology

Jul 2021 - Nov 2022 | Frontend Development Scholar at GREat - Computer Networks, Software Engineering, and Systems Group, UFC by FUNCAP

• Developing and maintaining web applications focused on order and process management for the Government of the State of Ceará;

Skills: React · HTML · SCSS (Sass) · Ant Design · Rest API · Scrum Methodology

Projects and Technologies

Click on the name of each project to access its respective GitHub repository.

- HTML and CSS:
 - Star Wars Dashboard | 2021
 - * Sample web application showcasing some information about the Star Wars franchise.
- React:
 - User Management Site | 2022
 - * Simple project for a user management interface.
 - Click Project Site | 2022
 - * Project for voting on movies for screening in a school or institution.
 - Country Quiz | 2022
 - * Quiz about countries with dynamic questions generated from an API with information about countries, cities, etc.
 - Tic-Tac-Toe Game | 2022
 - * Simple tic-tac-toe game to play with up to 2 players.
 - Vehicle Rental System Site | 2022
 - * Web page for using the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental agency in Quixadá.
- Angular:
 - MFE with Module Federation | 2023
 - * Testing the concept of Micro Frontends with Angular applications.
 - Trakto TV | 2023

- * Application built with the Trakto API.
- Dynamic Layout | 2023
 - * Application testing the concept of dynamic layout with Angular.
- Vue:
 - Poké Search | 2023
 - * Application to list and search for pokémons using the Poké API.
 - Vehicle Rental System Site | 2022
 - * Web page for using the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental agency in Quixadá.
- Node:
 - Click Project API | 2022
 - * Backend for the Click Project, a project for voting on movies for screening in a school or institution.
 - Vehicle Rental System API | 2022
 - * Backend for the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental agency in Quixadá.
- Java:
 - User Management API | 2022
 - * Backend for the project of a user management interface.
- Kotlin:
 - Vehicle Rental System App | 2023
 - * Native Android app for using the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental agency in Quixadá.

Skills

- Angular;
- Angular Universal;
- React:
- Node;
- Java;
- Typescript;
- Scss (Sass);
- Scrum;
- PostgreSQL;
- Prisma.

Education

2022 - Present | Bachelor's in Information Systems - UFC campus Quixadá - CE, Brazil

• Bachelor's degree in Information Systems with a focus on information system and web development.

2020 - 2022 | Bachelor's in Computer Engineering - UFC campus Quixadá - CE, Brazil (Interrupted)

• Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering with a focus on embedded systems using C and Assembly. Interrupted for change of course.

2017 - 2019 | Computer Networks Technician - IFCE campus Tauá - CE, Brazil

• Technical education in Computer Networks with skills in network administration, structured cabling, and computer maintenance.

Languages

- English Advanced
- Spanish Beginner
- Portuguese (Brazilian) Native

Portfolio and Contact (click to access)

- GitHub
- LinkedIn
- Online Resume
- Lattes Curriculum

This resume was created entirely in Markdown based on the example available at CV Example.